I: When was the last time you were at an airport?
S: Um, about a month ago.
I: Were you going somewhere or meeting someone?
S: I was meeting, um, my mother, who was, er,
she arrived at midnight, coming back from Tenerife.
I: Do you have any plans for tonight?
S: Er, yes, I do have plans for tonight.
I’m going to a party with some friends.
I: What housework do you hate doing?
C: I hate cleaning the bathroom, that’s my least favourite job around the house.
I: Is there anything you don’t mind doing?
C: I don’t mind cleaning the kitchen, because there’s usually a lot of food to eat.
I: Have you ever bought something online and had a problem?
A: I, I’ve bought clothes online that didn’t fit, but that’s about it.
I: How organized are you?
M: Er, not very.
Um, I tend to be fairly disorganized, but still get things done.
I: Have you ever missed a train or a flight?
M: Yes, yes. I was flying to Poland and didn’t wake up in the morning,
and got to the gate as the flight was leaving.